[{"answer": "Nothing. Except he wasn't kidding. Usually it's a fakeout, you probably know. They pretend to tie you up, and you wear a dress with a cloth belt and they pretend to whip you or you", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I can't say he was anybody", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Maybe, if you tell me the things you haven't", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Do you know where he got the dumper", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Is there anything more I could", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What're you gonna do next", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yeah, you got to me", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "If my friend is living with my friend", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "But if it's someone else I do", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I believed he", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " It's where it doesn't get me. I've got nothing left that connects to anything", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " Why", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "What if i go out on tricks", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "How can you do it to yourself", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Ligouri", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " All right. Loneliness.  Well", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "  Do you always have to repeat", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "All right", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Goodbye, my friend", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Yeah", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What am I supposed to say", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "With my friend", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Maybe I wasn't there when you called", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Maybe I wasn't there when you called", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " How do you know how bad it was", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Is that why my friend didn't tell me", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What was better? I made better bait", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yeah, two things my friend, that", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Yeah. It wasn't my friend", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " It probably has the Dumper's name. It might give us some kind of new lead.  I want a look at it anyhow", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "All right, but I'm going to see that list", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " No. I was going to come up. I wanted to ask you to marry me.", "docId": "klute.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I am", "qsentId": 34}]